Finding Aid for the Ernst Toch Papers PASC-M.0001
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Toch's Library: Scores, Series 10.
  - Published Works, Subseries 2.
    - Granites, 1935; 15 pages; piano score (Box 164, Folder 7)
      With Luening and Heilner pieces in same folder.
    - Second Rhapsody, 1935; 15 pages; piano score (Box 164, Folder 7a)
      Rudhyar and Luening pieces in same folder.
    - Klaviermusik Erster Teil Uebung in Drei Stuecken, op. 37, 1925; 23 pages; score (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - Kammersymphone Fuer 15 Soloinstrumente, op. 9, 1912; 56 pages; score (Box 164, Folder 9)
    - Palestrina, 1916; 369 pages; score (Box 164, Folder 10)
      Inscribed to Toch by the composer. Hans Pfitzner, editor.
    - Sonate Pour Violon et Piano, 1927; 9 pages; violin score (Box 164, Folder 11)
    - Quatre Nocturnes Pour Piano, 1952; 6 pages; score (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - USA 1946: Compositions for Piano by Contemporary American Composers, 28 pages; score (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Der Ferne Klang, 1911; 328 pages; score (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Cardillac. Mainz: B. Schott's Sohne, 1926., 179 p. score (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Goldmark, Carl. Ein Wintermaerchen. New York: Breitkopf & Haertel, 1907., 207 p. score (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Neues Vom Tage. Mainz: B. Schott's Sohne, 1929., 252 p. score (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai. Sonata Pour Violoncelle et Piano. Berlin: Russischer Musikverlag, n.d., 26 p. score (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Ravel, Maurice. Sonate pour violon et piano. Paris: Durand, 1927., 32 p. piano score (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - Klein, Walther. Sonate fuer Violine und Klavier., 27 p. score (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Weiller, Ludwig. Drei Klavierstuecke. Wuerzburg: Universitaetsdruckerei H. Sturtz A. G., 1927., 7 p. score (Box 166, Folder 12)
    - Frank, Otto R. Drei Mehrstimmige Gesaenge. Frankfurt: Druck Leo Schoenmann, n.d., Four leaves, three copies (total 12 leaves) (Box 166, Folder 13)
      1. Den flus entlang {Along the river} 2. Liedwerden 3. Lenz {Spring} Inscribed to Toch
    - Haendel, Georg Friedrich. Auswahl aus Seinen Klavierwerken. Walter Rehberg, ed. Stuttgart: J. G. Cottasche Buchhandlung Nachf., 43 p. (Box 166, Folder 14)
      Inscribed to Toch by the editor.
    - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai. Sonatine Pour Piano, op. 7. Berlin: Edition Russe de Musique, 1928., 19 p. score. (Box 166, Folder 16)
      Inscribed by the composer.
    - Klein, Walther. Anrufung. Innsbruck: Universitaets-Verlag Wagner, 1924., 8 p. score for violin & piano and violin part (1l) (Box 166, Folder 17)
      Inscribed to Lily Toch by the composer.
    - Antheil, George. Second Sonata, "The Airplane" for Piano Solo. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1931., 11 p. (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Brooks, Ernest. "Toccata" from 3rd piano Sonata. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1936., 16 p. piano score (Box 167, Folder 2)
      Siegmeister piece in same folder.
    - Siegmeister, Elie. The Strange Funeral in Braddock. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1936., 16 p. piano-vocal score (Box 167, Folder 2)
      Brooks piece in same folder.
    - Pfitzner, Hans. Von Deutscher Seele. Berlin: Verlag Adolph Fuerstner, 1921., 173 p. score (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Der Daemon. Mainz: B. Schott's Soehne, 1924., 72 p. score (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - Schreker, Franz. Christophorus. Leipzig: Druck C. G. Roeder A-G, 1931., 183 p. score (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - Rozsa, Bela. Sonate Pour Piano. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1936., 16 p. score (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - Tremblay, George. Two Piano Sonatas. Los Angeles: New Music Society of Calif., 1936., 12 p. score (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Luening, Otto. Only Themselves Understand Themselves. San Francisco: New Music Society of California, 1935., 15 p. piano score (Box 167, Folder 7b)
      Rudhyar and Heilner pieces in same folder.
    - Webern, Anton. Geistlicher Volktext fuer Eine Singstimme, Violine, Klarinette & Bassklarinette. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1930., 5 p. score (Box 167, Folder 8)
    - Tansman, Alexandre. Cinq Melodies pour Chant et Piano. Paris: La Sirene Musicale, 1928., 9 p. score (Box 167, Folder 10)
    - Miaskovsky, N. Fragment Lyrique. San Francisco: New Music Orchestra Series, 1934., 15 p. score (Box 167, Folder 11)
    - Ruggles, Carl. Sun-treader. San Francisco: New Music Orchestra Series, 1934., 51 p. score (Box 167, Folder 12)
    - Roldan, Amadeo. Motivos de Son. San Francisco: New Music Orchestra Series, 1935., 32 p. score (Box 167, Folder 13)
    - Creston, Paul. Seven Theses for Piano. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1935., 12 p. score (Box 167, Folder 14)
    - Riegger, Wallingford. Three Canons for Woodwinds. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1932., 28 p. score (Box 167, Folder 15)
      Strang piece in same folder.
    - Strang, Gerald. Mirrorrorrim. San Francisco: New Music Society of Calif., 1932., 28 p. score (Box 167, Folder 15)
      Riegger piece in same folder.
    - Debussy, Claude. La Troisieme pour Violin et Piano. Paris: Durand, 1917., 8 p. violin part, score (Box 167, Folder 16)
    - Debussy, Claude. Prelude de La Damoiselle Elue. Paris: Durand, 1909., 4 p. score (Box 167, Folder 17)
    - Debussy, Claude. Mouvement. Paris: Durand, 1905., 11 p. score (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Debussy, Claude. Reflets Dans L'eau. Paris: Durand, 1905., 7 p. score (Box 167, Folder 18)
    - Cowell, Henry. Concerto for Piano and Orchestra. Paris: Senart, 1931., 63 p. score (Box 167, Folder 19)
    - Donizetti, Gaetano. Don Pasquale, Komische Oper in 3 Akten. Wien: Carl Halinger qdm. Tobias, n.d., piano score, 223 p. (Box 167a, Folder 1)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Ach Herr, mich armen Sünder. Facsimilie of manuscript. Publisher data unknown. (Box 167a, Folder 2)
      Inscribed by Elise Steindorff (?).
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus. Die Zauberfloete. Randzeichnungen zu Mozart's Handschrift von Max Slevogt. Facsimilie of manuscript. Publisher information unknown. (Box 167a, Folder 3)
    - Brahms, Johannes. Ein Deutsches Requiem, op. 45. Leipzig: Ernst Eulenburg, n.d., 293 p. (Box 167a, Folder 4)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus. Collected Works: Requiem D moll, Symphonie in C dur, Symphonie in G moll, Symphonie in Es dur. Leipzig: Ernst Eulenberg, n.d. (Box 167a, Folder 5)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Friede auf Erden, op. 13. Koeln: Tischer & Jagenberg, 1912., 19 p. (Box 168, Folder 1)
    - Ahn, Eak Tai. Korean National Hymn. San Francisco: Korean National Association, 1930., 2 leaves, score (Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Pringsheim, Klaus. 21 Short Piano Studies for Beginners. Kyoeki Sinosha & Co. Ltd., 1941., 12 p. score (Box 168, Folder 3)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Pelleas und Melisande, op. 5. Wien: Universal-Edition A. G. 1920., 125 p. (Box 168, Folder 4)
    - Lortzing, G. A. Der Waffenschmied. Leipzig: C. F. Peters, n.d., 190 p. score (Box 168, Folder 5)
    - Lortzing, G. A. Zar und Zimmermann. Leipzig: C. F. Peters, n.d., 232 p. score (Box 168, Folder 6)
    - Lortzing, G. Alb. Der Wildschuetz. Wien: Universal-Edition, n.d., 245 p. score (Box 168, Folder 7)
      Komische oper in drei aufzuegen.
    - Haas, Joseph. Unterwegs. Mainz: B. Schott's Soehne, 1926., 32 p. score (Box 169, Folder 1)
      7 gedichte von Hermann Hesse fuer eine hohe singstimme und klavier
    - Chochem, Corinne. Jewish Holiday Dances. New York: Behrman House, Inc., 1948., 85 p. score (Box 169, Folder 2)
    - Ronell, Ann. A Song Out of Heaven (Chopin's nocturne in Eb, arr.). New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1940., 7 p. score (Box 169, Folder 3)
      Inscribed to Toch by arranger.
    - Ahn, Eak Tai. Sweet Sixteen. Philadelphia: Elkan-Vogel Co. Inc., 1935., 3 p. score (Box 169, Folder 4)
    - Ahn, Eak Tai. Arirang Hill. Philadelphia: Elkan-Vogel Co. Inc., 1935., 5 p. score (Box 169, Folder 5)
    - Siegmeister, Elie. American Sonata, for Piano Solo. New York: Edward B. Marks, 1945., 24 p. (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. "The Dove." Choral settings of poems by John Keats, op. 157. New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, 1954., 9 p. score (Box 169, Folder 7)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. Candide: Six Illustrations pour le Roman de Voltaire. Los Angeles, Delkas, 1947., 32 p. (Box 169, Folder 8)
    - Gershwin, George. Preludes for Piano. New York: New World Music Corp., 1927., 12 p. (Box 169, Folder 9)
    - Gershwin, George. Rhapsody in Blue. Henry Levine, arr. New York: Harms Inc., 1939., 3 p. (Box 169, Folder 10)
    - Folk Songs of the New Palestine, Series 1. "Kuma Echa, arr. Walter Sternberg. "Banu,"arr. Aaron Copland. New York: NIGUN, 1938., 6 p. 3 copies. (Box 169, Folder 11)
    - Folk Songs of the New Palestine, Series 2. "Hinne Achal'la Bachalili," arr. Paul Dessau. "Ale Giva," arr. Paul Dessau. New York: NIGUN, 1938., 6 p. 3 copies. (Box 169, Folder 12)
    - Folk Songs of the New Palestine, Series 3. "Bring e Briks," arr. Kurt Weill. "Day After Day," arr. Darius Milaud. New York: NIGUN, 1938., 6 p. 3 copies. (Box 169, Folder 13)
    - Folk Songs of the New Palestine, Series 4. "A Vatiach," arr. Ernst Toch. "Salenu al Ktefenu," arr. Stefan Wolpe. "Hashkediya Porachat," arr. Menashe Rabinovitz. "Tel Aviv," arr. by Stefan Wolpe. New York: NIGUN, 1938., 8 p. 2 copies. (Box 169, Folder 14)
    - Folk Songs of the New Palestine, Series 6. "Mi Yivneh," arr. Lazare Saminsky. "Tapuach Zahav," arr. Ernst Toch. "Dunam Po," arr. Frederick Jacobi. New York: NIGUN, 1939., 8 p. 3 copies. (Box 169, Folder 15)
    - Cowell, Henry. Antinomy for Piano. New York: Breitkopf & Hartel, 1922., 7 p. score (Box 169, Folder 16)
    - Cowell, Henry. Dynamic Motion for Piano. New York: Breitkopf & Hartel, Inc., 1921., 4 p. score (Box 169, Folder 17)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Ludus Tonalis. New York: Associated Music Pub. Inc., 1943., 60 p. score (Box 169, Folder 18)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Sonata for Piano Duet. London: Schott & Co., Ltd., 1938., 31 p. score (Box 169, Folder 19)
    - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai. Variations and Epilogue for Violoncello and Piano. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corp., 1948., 32 p. score (Box 169, Folder 20)
    - Cowell, Henry. Amiable Conversations for Piano. New York: Breitkopf & Hartel, 1921., 1 p. score (Box 169, Folder 21)
    - Milhaud, Darius. Le Bal Martiniquais, two pianos four hands. Los Angeles: Delkas Music Pub. Co., 1945., 24 p. (Box 169, Folder 22)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. 6 Kleine Klavierstuecke, op. 19. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1913., 8 p. score (Box 169, Folder 23)
    - Zeisl, Erich. Requiem Ebraico. New York: Transcontinental Music Corp., 1946., 35 p. vocal score (Box 169, Folder 24)
    - Various composers. Musik Der Zeit. Wien: iversal-Edition, 1922., Piano solo 40 p. score (Box 169, Folder 25)
      Works by: Casella, Bartok, Wellesz, Pisk, Buttring, Hauer Eisler and Schoenberg.
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Drei Klavierstuecke, op. 11. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1910., 14 p. score (Box 169, Folder 26)
    - Casella, Alfredo. Sinfonia, Arioso, Toccata per Pianoforte, op. 59. Milano: Carisch S.A., 1936., 27 p. score (Box 169, Folder 27)
    - Jean Wiener: "Blues, "Haarlem." Clement Doucet: "Six Cylinder Rag-Time," "Chicken Pie." Wien: Universal-Edition, 1929., 15 p. piano score (Box 169, Folder 28)
    - Tansman, Alexandre. Four Piano Moods. Los Angeles: Delkas Music Pub. Co., 1946., 7 p. score (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - Butting, Max. Fuenfzehn Kurze Klavierstuecke, op. 33. Wien: Universal-Edition A. G., 1928., 16 p. (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Fuleihan, Anis. Sonata no. 2. Los Angeles: Delkas Music Pub. Co., 1946., 11 p. score (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - Riegger, Wallingford. Cooper Square. New York: Pietro Deiro Publications, 1958., 9 p. score (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Rozsa, Miklos. Berceuse. New York: Associated Music Publishers, Inc., 1947., 3 p. score (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - Rozsa, Miklos. Zingara. New York: Associated Music Publishers Inc., 1947., 3 p. score (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - Rozsa, Miklos. Burlesque. New York: Associated Music Publishers Inc., 1947., 5 p. score (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Ives, Charles. Lincoln the Great Commoner. San Francisco: New Music Edition Orchestra Series, n.d., 16 p. score (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - Ireland, John. Ballade for Piano. London: Schott & Co., 1931., 11 p. score (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Ireland, John. Two Pieces for Piano: February's Child, Aubade. London: Schott & Co., Ltd., 1931., 7 p. score (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Vierte Symphonie in G dur, fuer Piano zu 4 Haenden. Wien: Ludwig Doblinger, n.d., 43 p. (Box 170, Folder 10)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Erste symphonie in D dur, fuer Piano zu 4 Haenden. Wien: Josef Weinberger, n.d., 83 p. (Box 170, Folder 11)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Das Lied von der Erde, Klavierauszug. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1912., 146 p. (Box 170, Folder 12)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Jonny Spielt Auf, op. 45. Klavierauszug mit text. Wien: Universal-Edition A. G., 1926., 206 p. (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Liszt, Franz. Symphonies de Beethoven, Partition de Piano. First edition (?). Leipzig: Breitkopf & Haertel, 1865., 214 p. (Box 170, Folder 13)
    - Zeisl, Erich. Kinderlieder. Wien: Capriccio-Verlag, 1933., 10 p. (Box 170, Folder 14)
    - Ronchetto, Louis. This Is Your Accordion. Oklahoma City: Ideal Publications, 1958., 36 p. method book (Box 171, Folder 1)
      Included: Letter to Toch from the American Accordionists' Association, Inc.
    - Schnabel, Artur. Symphony no. 1. New York: Edition Adler, 1945., 172 p. score (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Sharp, Cecil J. Country Dance Tunes from the English Dancing Master XI. London: Novello & Co., 1922., 26 p. (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Sharp, Cecil J. Morris Dance Tunes. London: Novello & Co., 1910., 29 p. (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Das Marienleben fuer Sopran und Kklavier, op. 27. Mainz: B. Schott's Sohne, 1924., 75 p. score (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Gurre-lieder. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1912., 238 p. score (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Achte Symphonie. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1910., 211 p. score (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Gruenberg, Louis. Negro Spirituals. Vol. 1. Wien: Universal Edition, 1926. (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Gruenberg, Louis. Negro Spirituals. Vol. 2. Wien: Universal Edition, 1926. (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Gruenberg, Louis. Negro Spirituals. Vol. 3. Wien: Universal Edition, 1926. (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - Gruenberg, Louis. Negro Spirituals. Vol. 4. Wien: Universal Edition, 1926. (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Lawrence, Lucile and Carlos Salzedo. Method for the Harp. New York: G. Schirmer, 1929., 71 p. (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Salzedo, Carlos. L'Etude Moderne de la Harpe. New York: G. Schirmer, 1921., 53 p. (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Tansman, Alexandre. Carnival Suite. New York: Leeds Music Corporation, 1945., 39 p. (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Tansman, Alexandre. Sonata No. 4 for Piano. New York: Associated Music Publshers, 1942., 23 p. (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Stockhausen, Karlheinz. Nr. 2 Klavierstuecke. London: Universal Edition, 1954., 14 p. (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - Prokofieff, Sergei. Die Liebe zu den Drei Orangen. Berlin: Breitkopf und Haertel, 1922., 252 p. score (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - Herrmann, Hugo. Vasantasena. Berlin: Ed. Bote & G. Block, 1930., 285 p. score (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - Rozsa, Miklos. Chinese Carillon. New York: Associated Music Publishers, 1947., 3 p. (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai. Concerto for Violin and Orchestra, op. 26. New York: Associated Music Publishers, 1944., 56 p. score and violin part (20 p.) (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Zeisl, Erich. Requiem Ebraico. New York: Transcontinental Music Corp., 1946., 35 p. vocal score (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - Raphael, Guenter. Sonata fuer Pianoforte, op. 28 nr. 2. Leipzig: Breitkopf & Haertel, 1939., 21 p. (Box 173, Folder 4)
      Inscribed to Miklos Rosza by the composer.
    - Schweizer, Gertrud. 20 Kleine Klavierstueke fuer di Jugend zu 2 Haenden. Kobenhavn: Wilhelm Hansen, Musik-forlag, 1932., 7 p. (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Cadman, Charles Wakefield. A Mad Empress Remembers, for cello and piano. New York: Mills Music, Inc., 1945., 32 p. score cello part (8 p.) (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - Rosza, Miklos. Sonate. Wiesbaden: Breitkopf & Haertel, 1948., 40 p. (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - Coolidge, E. S. Sonata for Oboe and Piano. Boston: Carl Fischer, Inc., 1952., 35 p. (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - Raphael, Guenter. Sonata fuer Pianoforte, op. 38, nr. 1. Leipzig: Breitkopf and Haertel, 1947., 25 p. (Box 173, Folder 9)
    - Sessions, Roger. Sonata for Piano. London: Schott and Co., 1931., 22 p. (Box 173, Folder 10)
    - Rosza, Miklos. Kaleidoscope for Piano Solo: March and Musette. New York: Associated Music Publishers, Inc., 1947., 3 p. each (Box 173, Folder 11)
    - Zeisl, Erich. Sonata Barocca. Wien: Verlag Ludwig Doblinger, 1955., 34 p. score for piano (Box 173, Folder 12)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Der Spring ueber den Schatten, op. 17. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1923., 196 p. score (Box 173, Folder 13)
    - Copland, Aaron. The Tender Land. Boosey & Hawkes, 1956., 203 p. score (Box 173, Folder 14)
      Inscribed to Toch by Erik Johns.
    - Wellesz, Egon. Alkestis, op. 35. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1923., 131 p. score (Box 173, Folder 15)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Dritte Symphonie in d moll. Wien: Universal-Edition, n.d., 231 p. score (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Symphonie Nr. 5. Leipzig: C. P. Peters, n.d., 251 p. score (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Stravinsky, Igor. Petroushka: A Burlesque in Four Scenes. London: Boosey & Hawkes, n.d., 152 p. score (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. "To Sleep." Choral Settings of Poems by John Keats, op. 157. New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, 1954., 9 p. (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Wagner, Roger. Mass in Honor of St. Francis. Los Angeles: Delkas Music Publishing Company, 1943., 19 p. (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Jacobi, Frederick. String Quartet on Indian Themes. New York: G. Schirmer, 1926., 36 p. score (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Helfman, Max. "L'cho Adonoy." Four Liturgical Pieces. New York: Transcontinental Music Corporation, 1950., 7 p. (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. Venice. New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, 1948., 11 p. score (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. The Fiery Furnace. New York: G. Ricordi & Co., 1959., 36 p. score (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Avshalomov, Jacob. How Long, Oh Lord. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, 1950., 35 p. score (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario. "Two or Three." Choral settings of poems by John Keats, op. 157. New York: Galaxy Music Corporation, 1954., 8 p. (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Reichenbach, Herman, ed. Classic Canons, for 2-6 Mixed Voices. New York: Music Press, 1943., 20 p. (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - Barber, Samuel. Overture to "The School for Scandal." New York: G. Schirmer, 1941., 36 p. score (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Streich-quartet, op. 7. Berlin: Verlag Dreililien, n.d., 16 p. incomplete (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. II Streich-Quartett, op. 10. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1919., 59 p. score (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Gurrelieder. (Fuehrer.) Leipzig: Universal-Edition, 1914., 45 p. score (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Verklaerte Nacht, op. 4. Berlin: Verlag Dreililien, n.d., 51 p. score (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Berg, Alban. Thematische Analyse Arnold Schoenbergs Kammersymphonie, op. 9. Leipzig: Universal-Edition, n.d., 15 p. analysis (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Milhaud, Darius. Le Bal Martiniquais pour Orchestre. Los Angeles: Delkas Music, 1946., 58 p. score (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Gershwin, George. Rhapsody in Blue. New York: Harms Inc., 1942., 47 p. score (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Fourth String Quartet, op. 37. New York: G. Schirmer, 1939., 107 p. (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Strauss, Richard. Symphonia Domestica, op. 53. Berlin: Bote & G. Block, 1904., 123 p. score (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Siebente Sinfonie. Berlin: Bote & G. Block, 1909., 257 p. score (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Schweizer, Gertrud. Sieben Marienlieder aus dem 16 Jahrhundert. Berlin: Verlagsanstalt Deutscher Tonkuenstler, 1929., 11 p. (Box 176, Folder 2)
      {Seven songs to the Virgin Mary from the 16th century, for one voice with piano accompaniment} Inscription.
    - Hindemith, Paul. Mathis der Maler. Mainz: B. Schott's Soehne, 1935., 283 p. score, program laid in (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - Cassado, Gaspar. Sonate Breve. Mainz: Schott's Soehne, 1931., 15 p. (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Ireland, John. Two Pieces for Piano: "February's Child." London: Schott & Co., 1931., 7 p. (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Sonate, op. 11 no. 2 in D, fuer Violine und Klavier. Mainz: B. Schott's Soehne, 1920., 11 p. (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Hindemith, Paul. Sonate, op. 11, nr. 1, fuer Violine und Klavier. Mainz: B. Schott's Soehne, 1918., 12 p. piano part, 4 p. violin part (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Pfitzner, Hans. Der Arme Heinrich, Ein Musikdrama in 3 Akten. Leipzig: Max Brockhaus, n.d., 159 p. score (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Krenek, Ernst. Orpheus und Eurydike, op. 21. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1925., 140 p. score (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Debussy, Claude. Reverie. Boston: G. Schirmer, 1909., 7 p. (Box 176, Folder 10)
      Analytic annotations by Toch.
    - Ravel, Maurice. Jeux d'eau, pour piano. Boston: BF Wood Music Co., 1905., 15 p. (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Drei Satiren fuer Gemischten Chor, op. 28. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1926., 58 p. score (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Vierte Symphonie in G dur. Wien: Ludwig Doblinger, n.d., 125 p. score (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Das Klagende Lied. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1912., 114 p. score (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Neunte Symphonie. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1912., 182 p. score (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Erste Symphonie in D dur. Wien: Universal-Edition, n.d., 171 p. score (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold. Pierrot Lunaire. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1914., 78 p. score (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Sechste Symphonie a moll. Leipzig: C. F. Kahnt Nachfolger, 1906., 263 p. score (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Zweite Symphonie in c moll. Leipzig: Friedrich Hofmeister, 1897., 209 p. score (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Mahler, Gustav. Achte Symphonie. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1911., 218 p. score (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Cummings, Arthur. Duo Para Violin y Viola. Santiago de Cuba: Universidad de Oriente, 1959., 29 p. (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Pfitzner, Hans. Das Christelflein. Berlin: Adolph Fuerstner, 1918., 152 p. (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Orgelpreludium und Fuge, klavier zu 2 haenden. Wien: Universal-Edition, 1912., 17 p. (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Chaconne in D moll. Busoni, ed. Leipzig: Breitkopf and Haertel, n.d., 19 p. (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Praeludien und Fugen. C. Reinecke, ed. Leipzig: Breitkopf und Härtel, n.d., 75 p. (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Das wohltemperierte Klavier, Erster Teil. Bruno Mugellini, ed. Leipzig: Breitkopf und Haertel, 1908., 115 p. (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Orgel-Kompositionen. Transcribed for piano by Franz Liszt. Heft 1. Leipzig: C.F. Peters, n.d., 31 p. (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Oregelfantasie und Fuge in G moll, bearbeitet von Franz Liszt. Magdeburg: Heinrichshofen's Verlag, n.d., 15 p. (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Chromatische Phantasie d moll. Berlin: Ed. Bote and G. Bock, 1905., 27 p. (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Konzert im Italienischen Stil, f dur. Berlin: Ed. Bote and G. Bock, n.d. (Box 178, Folder 11)